&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：外卖，或
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: A takeaway, or
一种总结的方法，如何避免这些角落的情况与双重相等。
a way to summarize, how to avoid these corner cases with the double equals.
这些是我认为你可以使用的一套指导原则。
These are a set of guidelines that I think you can use.
您可以使用Double Equals，但在这些特定情况下应避免使用。
You can use double equals, but avoid it in these particular scenarios.
第一，当两边都可以是0时，避免使用双等号，或者
Number one, avoid the double equals when either side of them can be a 0, or
空字符串，甚至是其中只有空格的字符串之一。
an empty string, or even one of those strings with only whitespace in it.
在这些情况下不要使用双等号。
Don't use double equals in those cases.
只是有很多角落的情况，你可能会被咬。
There's just a lot of corner cases that you might get bitten by.
有些人说，我不能，不。
Some people say well, I can't, no.
好的，但是你有没有重构你的代码，这样你就可以了？
Okay, but is there anyway for you to restructure your codes so you can?
因为我觉得这样更好。
Cuz I think that's better.
它至少是一个更好的代码，不管您是否喜欢double equals。
It's at least a better code, regardless of whether you like double equal or not.
但是假设你不能。
But let's say you can't.
嗯，那么另一张支票，你应该问或者
Well, then another check that you should ask or
为了避免双重相等，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：不要将它与
to avoid the double equals, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Don't use it with
非基本体。
non-primitives.
我甚至不会用它来比对他们的身份，
I don't even use it with the identity comparison on them,
尽管我知道这很管用。
even though I know it works.
但为了超级安全起见，我根本不对原语使用它。
But just to be super safe, I don't use it with primitives at all.
因此，如果我真的试图检查对数组的引用是否与
So if I was really trying to check is this reference to the array the same as
对数组的引用，我不会使用双等号。
this reference to the array, I'm not gonna use the double equals.
即使它会在一个特定的中心起作用，
Even though it would work in that one specific center,
它离边缘太近了，不值得。
it's close enough to the edge that it's not worth it.
这是我的外卖，或者我的偏好，好吗？
That's my takeaway, or my preference, okay?
因此，当它们是非原语时，不要使用double equals，只用于
So don't use the double equals when they're non-primitives, only use it for
原始人之间的强制。
coercion among the primitives.
而且绝对不要使用double等于true或double等于false。
And definitely don't use double equals to true or double equals to false.
本质上，只是允许ToBoolean发生，
Essentially, just allow the ToBoolean to happen,
无论如何，这是更好的结果。
which is the better outcome anyway.
或者如果你真的不能允许，如果它真的必须是真的或者
Or if you really can't allow that, if it really has to exactly true or
完全错误，有时确实如此，然后使用三重等于。
exactly false, which sometimes it does, then use triple equals.
这是一个相对较短的名单。
This is a relatively short list.
并且我会提出这样的情况，任何关心学习的开发人员
And I would make the case that any developer that cared to learn about
这些系统可以学习这个列表并有效地这样做，
these systems could learn this list and effectively do so,
在他们的代码中有效地传达他们正在避免这些问题。
effectively communicate in their code that they're avoiding these problems.